<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Blog Posts on nostyle.systems</title><link>https://no5tyle.github.io/blog/</link><description>Recent content in Blog Posts on nostyle.systems</description><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://no5tyle.github.io/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>A Khajit build log.</title><link>https://no5tyle.github.io/blog/en/a-khajit-build-log/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Jul 2022 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://no5tyle.github.io/blog/en/a-khajit-build-log/</guid><description>Khajit is a 60% o-ring gasket mount keyboard with a two piece housing construction. Featuring internal weight engravings, but a clean external weight, it’s almost a shame to cover up such cute engravings. Designed by Justterry, I was very excited to assemble a board by an Australian designer and a friend.
I built this board with TX 1.2t clip in stabilisers and broken in Kailh Cream switches. The switches have been spring swapped with 67g TX springs, using stock lubricant.</description></item><item><title>A minimal approach to optimising Topre.</title><link>https://no5tyle.github.io/blog/en/optimising-topre/</link><pubDate>Tue, 16 Nov 2021 12:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://no5tyle.github.io/blog/en/optimising-topre/</guid><description>Topre stands out in the enthusiast keyboard scene in many ways, in a sea of traditional ‘mechanical’ switches Topre is one of the few exceptions from the name most commonly used to describe the scene. An off-the-shelf, primarily plastic construction, with subdued aesthetics, it’s likely that Topre is not the first thing that springs to mind for most when discussing mechanical keyboards.
Many guides on customising your Topre experience lean into the extremely lubricated and silenced trend, however a large portion of the community, including myself, try to maintain a distance from this ideology.</description></item></channel></rss>